bytebx.com 2019-06-08

# ByteBX - online storage

## ByteBX Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to ByteBX. This privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to the ByteBX Web sites and Services and tells you how personal information is collected, used and disclosed by ByteBX. 

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

In order to provide our services, we collect the following types of information: 

##### Registration Information

When you register with ByteBX in order to create an account, we ask you to provide us with email address and account password. We may also ask you for billing information. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When you register, we also subscribe you to our mailing list to receive marketing emails such as promotions or special deals and newsletters. You may opt-out/unsubscribe at any time by logging into your account and updating your notifications settings. 

##### Children

In order to use the ByteBX services you must be at least eighteen (18) years of age. As children under the age of 18 are not allowed to use the ByteBX services, this Privacy Policy makes no provision for their use. 

##### User Communication

We will send you a welcoming email to verify your e-mail address. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to inform you about our services, and to manage your account, and for service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications. If you send us email or other communications, we may retain the content of your communications together with your email address and our responses. 

##### Cookies - Website Use Information

ByteBX uses "cookies" and other technologies to collect data that enable us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Website. Cookies are files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. If you do not want ByteBX to send cookies to your browser, you can set your browser options to reject cookies or to notify you when a Website tries to put a cookie into your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some features of ByteBX Products or Services. ByteBX gathers general information about visits to our Website, the files you have marked for backup, the configuration of your computer and your computer’s interaction with ByteBX, and stores this information in log files. ByteBX uses this information to understand traffic and downloads on our Website, enabling us to improve the site, provide the best online experience possible, and improve our ability to serve our customers. 

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

We use information which we collect for purposes of providing the services, auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services, ensuring the functioning of our servers, providing customer service, contacting you as described in this Privacy Policy, and to enable features of the services, such as to allow you to share photos and files with friends, and developing new products and services for our customers and prospective customers. We may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our services, respond to your support requests, and send you newsletters and special offers which we think you may find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by logging into your account and updating your notifications settings. Please keep in mind that by using our services, we may need to send you information regarding your account, such as service announcements, so by your use of our services, you authorize us to send you such information and you may not opt out of receiving those messages. 

##### Sharing Information with Third Parties

We do not share your files stored on our servers with any third parties unless instructed by you and allowed by ByteBX. We will not disclose your files to anyone unless you instruct us to do so or a court orders us to do so. Your files are not considered "personal information." ByteBX does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties except that your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in the following circumstances: \- When you have signed up for our services, we may disclose your personal information to our affiliates and subsidiaries to provide the services to you. \- We may use third parties to perform services related to our operations such as a payment processor, chat personnel, and an email service provider. In connection with these business operations, third parties may have access to your personal information. These third parties will be subject to an agreement to treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. \- We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our services and/or users of our services; (c) enforce the terms of use with respect to our services (including investigation of potential violations thereof); (d) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (e) protect the safety of users of the services, us or third parties. We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the average number of photographs being stored by users. Such information does not identify you individually. 

##### YOUR CONSENT

By using our services you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, subject to rights you may have as a subscriber to our services. If we change how we use your or your contacts personally identifiable information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should first contact support@ ByteBX.com.   
Updated: April 1, 2013
